our friend of the show Amanda seals is
still doing
interviews kicking Shannon's back really
yes no she's not don't L on her L like
that she is but it's a 5 minute clip
it's too long to play so I won't play it
I'm just letting y'all know that that is
still happening currently say same
talking points give me the points yeah
give me the points out of that all right
all right well she called the interview
an interrogation yeah okay her back was
against the wall she felt pressured into
yada yada y y there was no love in that
room back to the autism thing ah in her
defense of whatever she said about uh
diagnosing herself she ends up kicking
Shannon's back in
and I just want to say that talk
about this [ __ ] made me appreciate
Mo'Nique a little bit more man in what
way it just makes me appreciate Mo'Nique
a little bit more that you know she just
stands on her [ __ ] you know she a
Straight Shooters she had to interv with
Shannon sharp she he questioned a lot of
stuff that she said and she didn't she
just took it on her chin and it was a it
was an interview and Monique shade is
pray for brother Shannon I love him we
going to wrap our arms around shade
ain't about to be the victim mentality
[ __ ] got to stop yeah I got to stop I
hate it oh nobody gives a [ __ ] yeah you
got you went up there did you feel that
way when you was up there huh did you
feel that way that [ __ ] got millions of
views like why must it take a black
woman or whatever you are to go to black
man's platform and leave and kick him
down why that [ __ ] is trash for real
stop shanon Shar don't deserve that
[ __ ] if it was us then okay cool but sh
CH deserve
that that's the thing yeah if it was us
like see but that's the thing you making
you making a great point that I want to
add to and that's and that's the thing
and then I leave this alone right
like as somebody that destroys
relationships now seriously this is
important guys burn Bridges as somebody
that takes all the gas on the
bridge yourself he the tank I throw
gasoline parties come on y'all you
walking P that [ __ ] and walk back and
gas oh I throw gasoline Pary hey shout
out to whoever idea out there was to
come up with a paint party you [ __ ]
hey come over help me paint my [ __ ]
[ __ ] weirdo that's I've done it
before beer sound like fun though why
would you trust that everybody's going
to paint properly true you don't care
yeah
my [ __ ] getting painted I got [ __ ] done
oh yeah see that's some white people
chit y'all paint my [ __ ] right yeah if
we painting paint it right somebody got
to buy more paint and do do this again
don't leave the little bu don't leave
the bubbles in the dirt don't leave that
anyway ask somebody burn as somebody's
burn a lot of bridges the thing about
Amanda and Shannon is you got to know
when the person's back you kicking in is
like a really wellik back like people
[ __ ] with
Shannon everywhere so this that's why
you picked him Man of the Year podc you
picked him because this was supposed to
be your shot at Redemption so this is
just a master class in how to ruin what
was your Redemption
shot I don't think victims ever real no
not victims people that play or abuse
victimization ever realize what they're
doing she was supposed to go in there be
accountable smoke that [ __ ] and have
people looking at Amanda like cuz her
intelligence was clearly on she was
supposed to have [ __ ] looking at her
life judged her all wrong and and what
better time we looking for the the the
antithesis of
Candice we looking for the articulate
black well spoken that represents us
that's Pro black if if you can't get it
off now M you cooking I didn't even
think about that that was a good one n
but
[Music]